

# DOBROMIR HRISTOV

Front-end developer

dobromir92@gmail.com

+359 883 390 558

I am a dedicated web developer, with a passion for fast, reliable, cutting edge software with over 5 years of experience.

As a front-end developer, I have been exposed to many of the rapidly evolving technologies, frameworks, bundlers, preprocessors and UI/UX trends. I adhere to popular coding practices, deliver maintainable, well-engineered products. I implement testing and automation tools for speeding up development and reliability, allowing front-end teams to focus on coding.

I enjoy writing articles, open sourcing code, authoring libraries and teaching people.

## Experience

## Frontend developer (remote)

Sept 2017 - Present

### Hypefactors, Denmark

Web based software for PR professionals.

Started as a front end developer, solely developing and maintaining their Vue SPA blogging platform - Hype.news, later joined the development of the main Hypefactors product - a complex multilanguage Vue.js SPA with routing and shared state.

JS (ES2018, Vue.js/Vuex), Node.js, Pusher, Sass, Jest/Cypress testing, Webpack

## Web Developer

Jan 2016 – Aug 2017

#### Welldoers, Bulgaria

Web development agency.

I worked as a web developer, mainly responsible for the development of the front-end and partially contributing to the backend. Projects included ecommerce shops of various sizes, portfolios, Facebook Apps, product websites, WordPress and Laravel API driven Apps.

JS (ES2015, Vuejs/Vuex), Sass, Less, PHP (Laravel, WordPress)

#### Web Developer

Apr 2013 - Dec 2015

#### STSSoft, Bulgaria

Web development agency

Developed numerous public and private websites on various CMS and custom platforms. Worked both on front-end and back-end.

JS (jQuery), Grunt, Gulp, Brunch, Sass, PHP (Laravel, WordPress)

Education	
2011-2015	Technical University Gabrovo - Bachelor's degree Computer Systems Technology
Open Source Software	
Below is a selection of my open-source packages and Palettify	d contributions:

Configurable plugin to apply visual effects to images using their primary color palette.

A starter template to explain and ease the implementation of vue-i18n in to a Vue project.

Easy error message display using Vuelidate validator in Vue components.

Along with packages, I have written articles, contributed to documentations, even wrote a whole page in the official Vue multilingual library docs (vue-i18n) about Lazy loading translation files.

Vuelidate-error-extractor

Vue-i18n-starter